filesharingtalk.com 2004-06-03

# FileSharingTalk.com - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this web site. 

FileSharingTalk.com has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how FileSharingTalk.com collects information from users of FileSharingTalk.com services (the "Services"), how we use the information we collect and the choices you have concerning the collection and use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and other applicable laws. You must be 13 to use the Services. FileSharingTalk.com does not attempt to ask or collect information from any person under the age of 13. 

FileSharingTalk.com may have products and web pages designed especially for younger users under the direct supervision of an adult Member. While we make every effort to ensure that these Services are fun and age-appropriate for a younger audience, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision. For further information about tips, tools, age-appropriate or kid-friendly Web sites and how to report online trouble, please visit www.getnetwise.org 

At our website, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

**How We Use the Information**   
The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to analyze site usage or services. 

Administrators and Moderators of FileSharingTalk.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for FileSharingTalk.com 

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites**   
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**Public Forums**   
Any information that you disclose in public areas of our Web sites or the Internet may become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. 

**Cookies**   
To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas on our sites. We do not use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

**How to Contact Us**   
If you have any questions or concerns about the FileSharingTalk.com online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us. 

FileSharingTalk.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on our web site FileSharingTalk.com
